http://www.abe-online.com/abe-privacy-policy

Cart
Check SigningCheck Signing MachinesCheck Signing SoftwareSignature Plates, Ribbons, & SuppliesPositive Pay SoftwareBlank Check Stock FinderBottom checkPerf Location
7 1/2" - BOTTOM
CHECKSPerf Location(s)
4" and 7 1/2" - BOTTOM
CHECKSPerf Location(s) 3 2/3" and 7 1/3" - BOTTOM
CHECKSMiddle checkMIDDLE 3 1/2", 7" CHECKSMIDDLE 3 2/3", 7 1/3" CHECKSMIDDLE 4", 7 1/2" CHECKSTop CheckTOP 3 1/2", 7 1/2" CHECKSTOP 3 1/2", 7 1/4" CHECKSTOP 3 1/2", 7" CHECKSTOP 3 2/3", 7 1/3" CHECKSMICR Laser Toner CartridgesPaper ShreddersIndustrial Paper ShreddersLarge Office ShreddersMid-Size Office ShreddersSmall Office ShreddersHigh Security Micro-cut [NSA/CSS listed]Shredders on GSA ContractAutomatic Feed ShreddersOil Free ShreddersShredder Oil / Shredder Bags / Collection CartsShred Bins, Carts, ConsolesShredder BagsSmall to Medium Shredder BagsLarge Shredder Bags.Dahle Shredder BagsDahle 20381Dahle 20390Dahle 20392Dahle 20394Dahle 20396Dahle 20434Dahle 20506Dahle 20514Dahle 20606Dahle 20612Dahle 20614Dahle 20630Dahle 20634Dahle 20800Dahle 20801Dahle 20803Dahle 20813Dahle 20814Dahle 20822Dahle 20830Dahle 20831Dahle 20834Dahle 20835Dahle 30406Dahle 30414Dahle 30430Dahle 30434Dahle 40206Dahle 40214Dahle 40306Dahle 40314Dahle 40334Dahle 40406Dahle 40414Dahle 40434Dahle 40506Dahle 40514Dahle 40534Dahle 40606Dahle 40614Dahle 40634Dahle 41214Dahle 41314Dahle 41322Dahle 41330Dahle 41334Dahle 41414Dahle 41422Dahle 41430Dahle 41434Dahle 41514Dahle 41522Dahle 41530Dahle 41534Dahle 41614Dahle 41622Dahle 41630Dahle 41634Formax Shredder BagsHSM Shredder BagsHSM 125.2HSM 225.2HSM 386.2HSM 390.3HSM 411.2HSM FA400HSM FA450HSM FA490HSM FA500Intimus Shredder BagsIntimus 0077SEIntimus 007SIntimus 120Intimus 14.52Intimus 14.95Intimus 16.50Intimus 175Intimus 3190.4Intimus 380Intimus 390Intimus 402Intimus 407Intimus 421Intimus 424Intimus 430Intimus 431Intimus 434Intimus 444Intimus 4440Intimus 45Intimus 452Intimus 500Intimus 502Intimus 5034.4Intimus 5130.6Intimus 60Intimus 600Intimus 602Intimus 700Intimus 702Intimus 706Intimus 802Intimus 852Intimus 90Martin Yale Shredder BagsMartin Yale 1000Martin Yale 14.95Martin Yale 16.50Martin Yale 2000Martin Yale 3000Martin Yale 5000MBM Destroyit Shredder BagsAll other Destroyit and Ideal/MBM 10 inch to 12” throat openings modelsMBM Destroyit 2205MBM Destroyit 2206MBM Destroyit 2501MBM Destroyit 2502MBM Destroyit 2503MBM Destroyit 2600MBM Destroyit 2601MBM Destroyit 2602MBM Destroyit 2603MBM Destroyit 2604MBM Destroyit 3101MBM Destroyit 3102MBM Destroyit 3103MBM Destroyit 3104MBM Destroyit 3105MBM Destroyit 3800MBM Destroyit 3801MBM Destroyit 3802MBM Destroyit 3803MBM Destroyit 3804MBM Destroyit 4000MBM Destroyit 4001MBM Destroyit 4002MBM Destroyit 4003MBM Destroyit 4004MBM Destroyit 4005MBM Destroyit 4011MBM Destroyit 4012MBM Destroyit 4105MBM Destroyit 4202MBM Destroyit 4203MBM Destroyit 4605Olympia Shredder BagsOlympia 1000CCOlympia 1400 SeriesOlympia 1500 SeriesOlympia 1600 SeriesOlympia 1700 SeriesOlympia 1800 SeriesOlympia 2000CCOlympia 32CCSecurio Shredder Bags Securio B22 Securio B24412.2P36P40P44Securio
B32Securio B34Wilson Jones Shredder BagsWilson Jones 1000Wilson Jones 1500Wilson Jones 2000Wilson Jones 2500Wilson Jones 3000Wilson Jones 3500Wilson Jones A900Shredder OilHard Drive/ SSD DestructionDegaussersDisintegrator / Mixed Media DestroyerHard Drive CrushersHard Drive PunchesHard Drive ShreddersSSD, Cell Phone, PDA, Circuit Board DestructionCardboard Box ShreddersPaper HandlingCompactorsPaper FoldersPaper CreasersForm BurstersRotary paper trimmersGuillotine paper trimmerStack Paper CuttersPressure SealersCard SlittersPaper JoggersLetter OpenersPaper TabbersBooklet MakersDocument HandlingFurnitureFireproof File CabinetsFireproof SafesCurrency HandlingCoin & Bill CountersCounterfeit DetectionTime and Date StampsMore Equipment | SuppliesGSA Shredder SuppliesWireless lightsStaplersHole PunchesKobra | Parts and AccessoriesFormax | Parts and AccessoriesDESTROYIT & Triumph | Parts and AccessoriesPrintersBLOG
Search
More Info > Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions
Our 7 Day Money Back Guarantee applies to all products except items customized to customers specifications, internationally shipped items, or commercial paper cutters.  Restocking fees may apply to all returns.  Please ask an Advantage Business Equipment representative about purchasing under our money back guarantee program to determine if a product qualifies or if restocking fees apply.At Advantage Business Equipment, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect to assist us in processing orders. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.The Information We Collect: Advantage Business Equipment collects from you the necessary information, such as name, email address, address and payment information, to process orders.We Do Not Share Your Personal Information: Advantage Business Equipment does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. This information is for our private records only. We restrict access to your orders to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. Personal information is not available to any third party via our website or through other means.Spam Email and Use of Email Addresses: We make every effort to minimize the amount of email correspondence you receive from us. We do not share or sell your email address to any third parties.Use of Cookies: Advantage Business Equipment uses cookies to enhance your shopping and browsing experience and keep track of your order information. The cookies we use DO NOT store any personal information such as your e-mail address, street address or phone number.Do you still have questions? If you have additional questions or wish to further discuss details of our privacy policy, please feel free to Contact Us.Terms and Conditions ABE-Online.comIn using this website you are deemed to
have read and agreed to the following terms and conditions:The following terminology applies
to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and
any or all Agreements: "Client", “You” and “Your” refers to you,
the person accessing this website and accepting the Company’s terms and
conditions. "The Company", “Ourselves”, “We” and "Us",
refers to our Company. “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both the Client
and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves. All terms refer to the offer,
acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of
our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner, whether by
formal meetings of a fixed duration, or any other means, for the express
purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s
stated services/products, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing English
Law. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural,
capitalisation and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and
therefore as referring to same.Privacy Statement.  We are
committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized employees within the company
on a need to know basis only use any information collected from individual
customers. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best
possible service to our customers. Parliament has created specific offences for
unauthorised actions against computer systems and data. We will investigate any
such actions with a view to prosecuting and/or taking civil proceedings to
recover damages against those responsibleConfidentialityWe
are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and as such, any information
concerning the Client and their respective Client Records may be passed to
third parties. However, Client records are regarded as confidential and
therefore will not be divulged to any third party, other than our supplies if
legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities. Clients have the
right to request sight of, and copies of any and all Client Records we keep, on
the proviso that we are given reasonable notice of such a request. Clients are
requested to retain copies of any literature issued in relation to the
provision of our services. Where appropriate, we shall issue Client’s with
appropriate written information, handouts or copies of records as part of an
agreed contract, for the benefit of both parties.We will not sell, share, or rent your
personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for
unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by this Company will only be in connection
with the provision of agreed services and products.DisclaimerExclusions and Limitations
The information on this web site is provided on an "as is" basis. To
the fullest extent permitted by law, this Company:§excludes all representations and
warranties relating to this website and its contents or which is or may be
provided by any affiliates or any other third party, including in relation to
any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the Company’s literature;
and §excludes all liability for damages
arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes,
without limitation, direct loss, loss of business or profits (whether or not
the loss of such profits was foreseeable, arose in the normal course of things
or you have advised this Company of the possibility of such potential loss),
damage caused to your computer, computer software, systems and programs and the
data thereon or any other direct or indirect, consequential and incidental
damages. This
Company does not however exclude liability for death or personal injury caused
by its negligence. The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the
extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a consumer are
affected. PaymentCash or Personal Check with Bankers Card, all major
Credit/Debit Cards, Bankers Draft or BACS Transfer are all acceptable methods
of payment. Our Terms are payment in full within thirty days. All goods remain
the property of the Company until paid for in full. Monies that remains
outstanding by the due date will incur late payment interest at the rate of 2%
above the prevailing Bank of England's base rate on the outstanding balance
until such time as the balance is paid in full and final settlement. We reserve
the right to seek recovery of any monies remaining unpaid sixty days from the
date of invoice via collection Agencies and/or through the Small Claims Court
in the event that the outstanding balance does not exceed $3000. In such
circumstances, you shall be liable for any and all additional administrative
and/or court costs. Returned checks will incur a $25 charge to cover banking fees
and administrative costs. In an instance of a second Returned check, we reserve
the right to terminate the arrangement and, if agreed to, we shall insist on
future cash transactions only. Consequently, all bookings and/or transactions
and agreements entered into will cease with immediate effect until such time as
any and all outstanding monies are recovered in full.
Availability Unless
otherwise stated, the services featured on this website are only available
within the CONTUS.. All advertising is intended solely for the United States
market. You are solely responsible for evaluating the fitness for a particular
purpose of any downloads, programs and text available through this site.
Redistribution or republication of any part of this site or its content is
prohibited, including such by framing or other similar or any other means,
without the express written consent of the Company. The Company does not
warrant that the service from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error
free, although it is provided to the best ability. By using this service you
thereby indemnify this Company, its employees, agents and affiliates against
any loss or damage, in whatever manner, howsoever caused.Log FilesWe use
IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and
gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not
linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems
administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web
servers automatically log standard access information including browser type,
access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. This information is
not shared with third parties and is used only within this Company on a
need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable information related to this
data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your
explicit permission.CookiesLike
most interactive web sites this Company’s website uses cookies to enable us to
retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our
site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people
visiting. Some of our affiliate partners may also use cookies. Links to this website
You may not create a link to any page of this website without our prior written
consent. If you do create a link to a page of this website you do so at your
own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your
use of this website by linking to it.Links from this website
We do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are
linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such
websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be
regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we
are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We
encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the
privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and
trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through
this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This
Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever
manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of
personal information.Copyright Notice Copyright
and other relevant intellectual property rights exists on all text relating to
the Company’s services and the full content of this website. This
Company’s logo is a registered trademark of this Company. The brand names and
specific services of this Company featured on this web site are trade markedCommunicationWe have
several different e-mail addresses for different queries. These, & other
contact information, can be found on our Contact
Us link on our website or via Company literature or via the Company’s
stated telephone, facsimile or mobile telephone numbers.Force MajeureNeither party shall be
liable to the other for any failure to perform any obligation under any
Agreement which is due to an event beyond the control of such party including
but not limited to any Act of God, terrorism, war, Political insurgence,
insurrection, riot, civil unrest, act of civil or military authority, uprising,
earthquake, flood or any other natural or man made eventuality outside of our
control, which causes the termination of an agreement or contract entered into,
nor which could have been reasonably foreseen. Any Party affected by such event
shall forthwith inform the other Party of the same and shall use all reasonable
endeavours to comply with the terms and conditions of any Agreement contained
herein.WaiverFailure of either
Party to insist upon strict performance of any provision of this or any
Agreement or the failure of either Party to exercise any right or remedy to
which it, he or they are entitled hereunder shall not constitute a waiver
thereof and shall not cause a diminution of the obligations under this or any
Agreement. No waiver of any of the provisions of this or any Agreement shall be
effective unless it is expressly stated to be such and signed by both Parties.GeneralThe
laws of California govern these terms and conditions. By accessing this website
you consent to these terms and conditions and to the exclusive jurisdiction of
the California courts in all disputes arising out of such access. If any of
these terms are deemed invalid or unenforceable for any reason (including, but
not limited to the exclusions and limitations set out above), then the invalid
or unenforceable provision will be severed from these terms and the remaining
terms will continue to apply. Failure of the Company to enforce any of the
provisions set out in these Terms and Conditions and any Agreement, or failure
to exercise any option to terminate, shall not be construed as waiver of such
provisions and shall not affect the validity of these Terms and Conditions or
of any Agreement or any part thereof, or the right thereafter to enforce each
and every provision. These Terms and Conditions shall not be amended, modified,
varied or supplemented except in writing and signed by duly authorised
representatives of the Company.Notification of ChangesThe
Company reserves the right to change these conditions from time to time as it
sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any
adjustment to these terms. If there are any changes to our privacy policy, we
will announce that these changes have been made on our home page and on other
key pages on our site. If there are any changes in how we use our site
customers’ Personally Identifiable Information, notification by e-mail or postal
mail will be made to those affected by this change. Any changes to our privacy
policy will be posted on our web site 30 days prior to these changes taking
place. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement on a regular basisThese terms and conditions form part of
the Agreement between the Client and ourselves. Your accessing of this website
and/or undertaking of a booking or Agreement indicates your understanding,
agreement to and acceptance, of the Disclaimer Notice and the full Terms and Conditions
contained herein. Your statutory Consumer Rights are unaffected. © ABE-Online 2015 All Rights Reserved
Federally Authorized
Authorized supplier for GSA Federal Supply Service on select models. State, Municipal and School Purchase Orders Accepted.
Have a Question?
Name
Company (if applicable)
© Copyright 2020 Advantage Business Equipment. All rights reserved.
